<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WhiteBeakGang</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/</link><description>Recent content on WhiteBeakGang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whitebeakgang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WhiteBeakGang Live October 3rd on Cock Talk Podcast -- Don't Miss It</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/wbg-live-on-cock-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/wbg-live-on-cock-talk/</guid><description>The Coop Collective will be featuring WhiteBeakGang this Sunday on the Cock Talk Podcast.
There will be giveaways and special surprises for those that tune in live! If you are already in WBG and can&amp;rsquo;t make it live, don&amp;rsquo;t worry as there will be something for you guys too!
Remember that you will need to follow both @WhiteBeakGang and @cocktalkderby on twitter and join the WBG Discord
Read below for more details on the event and how to qualify!</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the White Beak Gang</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:55:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/welcome/</guid><description>We have a ton of things planned and are excited to share them with you! Stay tuned!</description></item><item><title>2 Factor Authentication</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/2fa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/2fa/</guid><description>Passwords get compromised all the time and networks are not always secure 2 Factor Authentication (2FA) adds an additional layer of security when accessing apps/services online When 2FA is enabled, you will need to approve requests using a pin/code/push from a third party application Having 2 layers of security helps prevent your accounts and assets from being compromised if your credentials are exposed Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>3..2..1.. Website Activated.. Not just for WhiteBeaks!</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-website/</guid><description>Date Status September 25th 2021 Complete Of course you’ll find your WhiteBeak official news and updates from the WhiteBeak Community.
But you’ll also find information on our Official Partners, our Showcase of Merchandise, Roadmap, Blogs and more!
There’s a few more surprises up our sleeve.. Coming Soon!!
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>Bawku.. Hawku for Chickens!</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/chicken-analysis-websites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/chicken-analysis-websites/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Progress The amazing market analysis that Hawku provides for the ever so popular Zed Run is desperately needed for our Chickens! No one understands this more than us!
So, WhiteBeakGang is building it! Our new Bawku project will be open to the community, not just WhiteBeak members.
The WhiteBeakGang wants to ensure that the entire Chicken Derby Community is able to access this bank of information so that everyone can view the data and make well-informed decisions on how to manage your coop.</description></item><item><title>Best Practices</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/best-practices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/best-practices/</guid><description>Security is a team effort requiring us all to be diligent about identifying, addressing, and informing others as to potential security risks Never click links you don&amp;rsquo;t recognize and always double check links you do recognize to ensure the destination address is fully correct Always verify the person messaging you in your DMs is the person you think it is and not an impostor pretending to be someone else Keep your device software up to date to prevent security vulnerabilities from being exploited Never leave your device unattended to avoid physical compromise of your systems Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>Contests, Giveaways and Merch</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-giveaways/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-giveaways/</guid><description>Date Status September 12th 2021 Complete You&amp;rsquo;re missing out if you&amp;rsquo;re not joining our contests and giveaways.
Would you like one of our WhiteBeak coffee mugs? Want to win some Chickens for the Derby? How does winning another WhiteBeak sound?
Come on in and join the games, share some laughs, create a meme and have some fun.
Loads of contests and giveaways for our WhiteBeak Merch and other items in the 🎉Giveaways channel.</description></item><item><title>Discord and Direct Messages</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/discord-and-direct-messages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/discord-and-direct-messages/</guid><description>Discord is one of the most popular platforms for Blockchain, Crypto, and NFTs. Many Discord integrations prompt you to connect metamask or enter some other potentially sensitive information. It&amp;rsquo;s important to be cautious when using this platform and clicking links or interacting with bots. Direct Messages containing spammy and potentially malicious links are common and must be treated appropriately. Always verify Direct Messages you receive are truly from the person you think and not someone posing as a trusted individual.</description></item><item><title>Join us on Discord</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/public-discord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/public-discord/</guid><description>Date Status September 4th 2021 Complete It&amp;rsquo;s all about Community! WhiteBeak holder or not&amp;ndash;everyone is welcome.
Our Discord is designed to enhance the Chicken Derby experience and bring together like-minded derby enthusiasts for teamwork and support.
Come chat, learn, strategize and join the fun!
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>Keyloggers and Malware</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/malware/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/malware/</guid><description>Software designed for a malicous purpose is referred to as Malware Malware comes in many forms and may infect your devices in different ways Keyloggers are a type of malware that monitor your typing and record keystrokes being sent to your keyboard This data can be sent to other servers to people looking to abuse this info (credit cards, passwords, contacts, recovery seeds) Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>Malicious Smart Contracts</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/malicious-smart-contracts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/malicious-smart-contracts/</guid><description>Just like traditional software applications, a dApp may also contain vulnerabilities. These may sometimes be accidentally introduced through inexperienced or careless developers or intentially by more malicious parties. A malicious smart contract may attempt to trick you into paying an exorbitant amount of crypto to the contract/address or transfer your other assets/NFTs against your will. Enabling 2 Factor and using a Hardware Wallet are critical steps to prevent being vulnerable to these exploits.</description></item><item><title>Passwords</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/passwords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/passwords/</guid><description>Keep your passwords safe and secure. Make sure you are not reusing passwords across many sites. Utilize a password manager to generate and keep track of hard to remember passwords for more security. Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to a great article on Wired about the best Password Managers out there:
Best Password Managers
Some top picks include:
1Password Bitwarden Dashlane Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>Phishing and Social Engineering</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/phishing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/phishing/</guid><description>Social Engineering is the practice of using someone&amp;rsquo;s natural behaviors and tendencies against them Social Engineering is often employed to get the target individual to reveal/disclose sensitive information they otherwise would not share Phishing uses Social Engineering techniques to get a target to provide access to account credentials Phishing attacks can be very sophisticated and clever in their design requiring you to be aware of these risks and to be on the lookout for suspicious clues and red flags Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>Random NFT Airdrops</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/random-nft-airdrops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/random-nft-airdrops/</guid><description>After some time in the NFT space you will from time to time notice a random NFT in your account that you do not recognize. These airdropped NFTs tend to be scams and are involved in a variety of attacks. A dusting attack will track wallets that attempt to spend or sell these assets which allows the trackers to deanonymize wallet addresses and better social engineer them. Potentially malicious smart contracts may also be connected to these NFTs that will prompt you to transfer crypto and other assets out of your wallet when attempting to sell or transfer the airdropped NFT.</description></item><item><title>Scams</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/scams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/scams/</guid><description>As with any potentially profitable field, there are many scammers in the Crypto, Blockchain, and NFT space. If an offer sounds too good to be true, it generally is too good to be true and should be approached with extreme skepticism. Always check with other trusted communities when presented with something that seems like a scam. Scams are only effective when the targets don&amp;rsquo;t know what to be on the lookout for.</description></item><item><title>Snacks are on us!</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-snacks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-snacks/</guid><description>Date Status September 4th 2021 Complete We work long and Play hard. To make sure we keep that little edge The WhiteBeaks provide free snacks and energy through the ☕️free-snacks channel in our Discord.
Early morning, late night or when you need a little extra refueling, grab a coffee on us and let’s keep working!
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>Software and Hardware Wallets</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/crypto-wallets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/crypto-wallets/</guid><description>Software wallets such as Metamask and Coinbase Wallet exist as programs/browser extensions on your devices and often are partly custodied with a third party Hardware wallets like Ledger and Trezor run on physical devices with your private keys stored on the device instead of your connected devices or online Connecting a hardware wallet to a software wallet like Metamask allows the hardware wallet to be used as a 2FA device requiring you to approve transactions both in the software and on the physical device Using the combination of a Software and Hardware wallet allows you to conveniently access your favorite dApps without compromising on security Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>VPNs and Network</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/vpn-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/security/vpn-networks/</guid><description>Avoid using public/shared networks if possible. If a public/shared network must be used, make sure you have a VPN set up to keep you safe. VPNs will encrypt your traffic and prevent others from intercepting your requests or seeing your data. Back to Security Module</description></item><item><title>WhiteBeakGang DAO</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-dao/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-dao/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Planning Our DAO is on the way!
This will be a collaborative approach to asset management amongst our team members.
More details will be coming soon on how to join and qualify for our DAO.
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WhiteBeakGang Incubator</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-incubator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-incubator/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Planning This is all for our community.
The Incubator&amp;rsquo;s mission is to provide the necessary network of resources and support to help jump start even MORE community projects!
Talk to us about your project and we&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do.
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WhiteBeakGang Token Launch</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-token-launch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-token-launch/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Progress You heard that right!
These limited edition tokens will be used to grant access to the WhiteBeak Community as well as qualify you for even MORE games, contests and giveaways!
We have some other utilities we’re working on. Stay Tuned! More to come..
Back to Roadmap</description></item></channel></rss>