<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>White Beak Gang</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/</link><description>Recent content on White Beak Gang</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whitebeakgang.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WhiteBeakGang Live October 3rd on Cock Talk Podcast -- Don't Miss It</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/wbg-live-on-cock-talk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/wbg-live-on-cock-talk/</guid><description>The Coop Collective will be featuring WhiteBeakGang this Sunday on the Cock Talk Podcast.
There will be giveaways and special surprises for those that tune in live!
Read below for more details on the event and how to qualify! Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out!
Cock Talk is back this Sunday Night with a very special guest, #WhiteBeakGang&amp;#39;s very own @DanielSmithDev!
We&amp;#39;ll talk naming, dev blog, and dive deep into what Daniel has planned for the community with the White Beak Gang.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the White Beak Gang</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:55:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/posts/welcome/</guid><description>We have a ton of things planned and are excited to share them with you! Stay tuned!</description></item><item><title>Know Your Chickens / Bawku</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/chicken-analysis-websites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/chicken-analysis-websites/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Progress The popular sites for doing horse analysis and market research in Zed Run are desperately needed for Chicken Derby as well so WhiteBeakGang will be building them!
These will be open to the entire community so that everyone will be able to access this info to make more informed decisions.
Read More</description></item><item><title>Public Discord</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/public-discord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/public-discord/</guid><description>Date Status September 4th 2021 Complete The WhiteBeakGang has opened a public Discord for all of it&amp;rsquo;s members and the larger community.
This is to provide a place to plan and discuss things as a team and work together to achieve our goals.
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WBG Giveaways</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-giveaways/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-giveaways/</guid><description>Date Status September 12th 2021 Complete WhiteBeakGang Merch and other Giveaways have started for all WBG members. These can be found in the public Discord in the 🎉Giveaways channel. They are free to enter so make sure you are taking full advantage!
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WBG Incubator</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-incubator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-incubator/</guid><description>WhiteBeakGang Incubator Date Status To Be Announced In Planning The WhiteBeakGang is a chance for WBG to help jump start community projects by providing the necessary network of resources to support their endeavors.
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WBG Snacks</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-snacks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-snacks/</guid><description>Date Status September 4th 2021 Complete Working on adding value to a community is tough work and the WhiteBeakGang wants to make sure everyone has the energy needed to power through. Check out the ☕️free-snacks channel in the Discord to refuel! The snack account will be refilled weekly so grab a coffee and chat a while with your fellow WhiteBeaks.</description></item><item><title>WBG Token Launch</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-token-launch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-token-launch/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Progress These limited edition tokens will be used to grant access to the WBG community and qualify people for various activities. More details regarding the various utilities to come soon. Stay tuned!
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WBG Website Launch</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-website/</guid><description>Date Status September 25th 2021 Complete The website you are visiting now has been put together to be a singular place to find official news and updates being shared from the WhiteBeak community. Visit here to see our official Partners, Merch Showcase, Roadmap, and recent blog posts and stay up to date on all things WBG.
Back to Roadmap</description></item><item><title>WhiteBeakGang DAO</title><link>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-dao/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whitebeakgang.com/roadmap/wbg-dao/</guid><description>Date Status To Be Announced In Planning The WhiteBeakGang DAO! A collaborative approach to asset management among team members. More details to come on how to join and qualify.
Back to Roadmap</description></item></channel></rss>